special effects hero actor
(on a) journey of transformation
special edition
Camping in Akihabara
yay
The three of us. Actually, a historical drama that starts in April.
Kimi to Yuki Teisaku to appear in Shinsengumi Seishun 6
I appreciate it.
Thank you.
All three of you are amazing.
Because the three of us did it before it was decided at all.
So, to commemorate our drama collaboration...
Totaro said he wanted to go camping with the three of us.
it has been decided (so) that
So here we are, just off the main street of Akihabara.
Camping practice campus under the elevated urban center
Totaro, have you ever been camping?
When I was in elementary school, did you have to go to school once a week?
Saturday and Sunday, go to the campground.
I've never been camping.
It's really not there.
We are now under the elevated railway.
There's a train going by.
There's a train barreling by above us.
Of course, you can camp here, barbecue, and so on.
I heard that you can even sleep over.
Sleeping in?
It's true, trains don't move at night, so it's perfect.
I'll get up on the first train and dance.
That's right.
I don't think there's anything wrong with that.
They fall at the same time.
It's just that it's such a mysterious space.
Indeed.
See.
This is so huge.
No, really.
It's hard to believe it's this big.
We're a family of four, and we're about two sizes smaller than this.
I think this is pretty big.
Then let's make this tent ourselves.
Let's go.
Cooperation.
Yes, sir.
But first, it's makeover time!
From here, the three of us played a game against each other.
One of the lowest ranks is forcibly transformed into a Yankee gym teacher.
Confrontational games are the new standard for camping fun.
Molook.
Have you heard of it?
I've heard of it.
I have one too.
I'm the only one missing.
I'm just trying to get an idea of what kind of game it is.
Like a KenKenpa.
Then why not just use KENKENPA?
You can't even get out.
Here we go.
(something that looks) hard to do
Throw Molook stick from a distance
The number of fallen skittles is scored.
This time, the goal is reached when the total is exactly 30 points.
Buber firm ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
It's nice to have a fire, but it's too cold for real.
I say, "If there is one, you should throw it like this.
Ohhhh, they're going to make me up.
You're soaking wet.
Well, follow me, Totaro.
I'll scatter for now. I'll...
please
Good!!!
10 points for this
Then 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10
11 points
So, we're going to rebuild this.
He said he'd get back up on the spot.
OK
A little scattered.
Isn't this hard to do?
This is Muzu!
If you hit it, it feels really good.
Mork's score is more than just how many sticks you can knock down.
If only one stick is knocked down
The number written on the stick is the score as it is.
Up to 12 points can be earned at a time
If you exceed the target of 30 points, you have to start over from 15 points, which is half of the target.
Be on your guard even when reaching for the
Then came the fifth pitch, with a big eye reaching for it.
WHEREAS.
I really don't want to lose this one, so I'm solid.
How many points are you at now, little boy?
I'm going steady for a bit.
I see... so if we decide on one 12th place, we'll go for it.
But, you know, it would be cool to take one of those down.
It's cool.
It's really cool.
Here we go.
Please, please, please, please.
I'm not going to lose today.
Please, please, please.
evil laughter
oh no (used as an expression of despair or when giving up)
amazing (e.g. of strength)
here it comes (interjection used when lying in wait for something)
I'm not getting it, I'm getting it, I'm getting it.
No, it's not.
No, I didn't.
I just got it.
No, it's not.
I waited and saw that I won, and then I came.
Here we go.
Wait a minute.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no.
I'm going to rip it off.
seriously
I'll check it out.
The momentum of the throw is walking straight out of the line.
This is totally out of line.
But wait, he's gone 12 that far.
then
Okay, I'm still good.
I, myself (pompously)
Then three players reached and it was a close game.
low (position)
successful
All you have to do is score 7 points.
Seven points.
But they're all getting close.
OK
eighteen
7 drop in a soft orbit.
drop seven
I'll go.
Wow!
Nice try!!!
Three!
But you're getting close.
I'm going to take a shot.
11 or 12
Crack in the Reach
If I get 12, do I win?
If we can get that.
Ooh! Ooh! Ooh!
- Like a home run declaration. Sashima: Let's go!
- Let's go!
- If you get 10 people, you're a hero.
- No, I'll really do my best! Just a minute.
- I'm coming! - This takes a lot of strength.
- Ho!
- Ho! - I'm going! - This takes a lot of strength.
- Ho! - Ho!
- Yes! Yes!
- Seriously? - Hey - うま!
- Seriously? - I'm glad you're that far away. - Thank you.
- Seriously? ! - That's amazing. Seriously.
- Hunch is out of the race and from here on out it's a race to the bottom.
Maki Univ. scores 4. Totaro scores 2, then goal.
- Four, four, four, four...
- No. - You're going?
- Because you only have to knock down four of them, right?
- Knock down four of them. Just.
- It's more amazing than I thought.
- This is hard. - It's really hard.
- I'm going!
Thank you for watching!
Two.
two (long cylindrical things)
me
My
two places
My two.
You're flying too fast, Mokkun.
alright
That was about all I could do right now.
We are.
That's 2-2!
Let's make the winner the one who beats that thing.
I'm really talking about it.
I'm going for that one.
That's cool.
That's what I meant too.
Of course that's what he meant to do.
a man's game
The one who beats that one wins, right?
isn't it?
Let's go.
Now that I've said it, let's get it done in one shot.
this is difficult
This is realistic.
Realistic.
what are your thoughts on the matter?
Let's have fun.
I'll be there.
must not
Wow.
wonderful (e.g. of a meal)
Did you go?
good feeling
wonderful (e.g. of a meal)
This is a complete defeat.
We've already lost a big load.
Transformation!
You're late.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
you all
Yes, I'm sorry.
Do you know how long I've kept you waiting?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No. Sorry.
Really.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You're smiling.
No, I'm not laughing.
Oh, you're so pompous.
They found out.
Here we finally go to tent making.
Then let's make it.
Yes, sir.
Large tents
Can three amateurs make it right?
this (indicating an item near the speaker, the action of the speaker, or the current topic)
Yes, sir.
First of all, we spread out the tent fabric.
Spread Spread it out Spread it out
It's on the side here. Hold this one here. This one here.
OK
This is already in the way.
Out of the way.
And then I got a pole. I got a pole in there.
It's like we're assembling more and more.
- It's like a nunchuck.
oh, yes!
- Should I just stretch it out? - Yes.
Here. So, put it together.
Make it one.
I think you've started something big.
So, on the ground.
- Oh, sorry, Potcher.
Wow, it's like a circle of wisdom.
Stretch it out on the ground or something.
This goes in like this as a prop, crossed out.
- Oh, I see...
- Do you want me to start here and work my way through? - Yes.
posthumous honors
Then you can put it down once.
heave, ho!
with a grinding noise
in spite of
Push it, push it, push it, push it, push it, push it, push it.
Wait a minute. Up, up, up.
Good luck. Hold on a second.
Good luck. Good luck.
This way, too, go, go, go, go.
Wow, wow, wow, wow!
Yes, I'm in. OK.
Yes, nice. OK.
Half completed OK
So, what's this? Oh, I see.
So, if you put it on, that means it's going to clank.
I see. Yes, yes, yes.
Can I put it in with "Se-no"?
Yeah, you can go in.
There we go. All at once. There we go.
Finally, click, click, click.
Okay, okay, okay. Wow.
Oh, great! It's done for now!
yay
No, it's easier than I thought.
Tents are so easy to make.
But it's really done. - Shall we go in?
Are you in? I'm curious. I'm curious. I'm curious.
Here's the front door.
Come on, let's go further.
Hey, Total, you'd be surprised, wouldn't you?
This is great, isn't it? This is great.
Here we go. - Ready, go, go!
Wow, amazing, amazing, amazing!
I like this one. Look at this one.
ready, go!
Wow, how do you like it? - It's a bed.
No, it's a bed. It's amazing.
It's a bed.
I'm cold too. You better come in.
Well, I'll leave you to it.
Oh, sorry. I only have two more.
Is it hopeless?
There are only two.
Why, already?
I really don't want to.
Oh, my God. Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Are you sure? Sure, sure, sure. Excuse me.
this (indicating an item near the speaker, the action of the speaker, or the current topic)
Hey, don't look at me.
Why are you looking at me?
Unfortunately, the weather was not good.
Cannot be spread
I couldn't.
This one is not only for the living room and bedroom.
A veranda area can also be created.
It's excellent.
Once the bed is ready, go to meal preparation.
Looks delicious!
When it's nice and cooked, add water.
excuse me
You can put it all in.
I was making it.
curry and rice
Do you have any recent episodes of Mr. Kan?
That's how it works. There's three of us, all going to you.
Sure, how about a secret episode of "You Go, You Go"?
There really haven't been any episodes lately.
The most important thing is that I enjoy being with everyone.
Well, that's the best thing, really.
I mean, I'm finally getting along with this, you know, YouTube thing, but...
The three of us who have become good friends are getting to know each other even better again in Kyoto.
That's what makes me happy.
I think it's a dream come true to be in a film together as actors of the same age.
It's kind of a friendly competition.
Not only are they close.
I think it's also good that it's a little bachi-bachi, and I think it's good that it's a little bachi-bachi.
We probably had a lot of fun today.
Maybe I'll go with you and make it.
I think he's serious.
The look on our faces.
I think you can see it.
Historical Dramas in which we will appear
Kimi kimi wo yukite saku Shinsengumi Seishunroku" (Kimi to go and bloom Shinsengumi Seishunroku) will finally begin!
It is an emotional portrayal of the young ambassadors gathered at the Shinsengumi as they run toward their dreams.
Kimi kimi wo yukite saku Shinsengumi Seishunroku" will start on Wednesday, April 24th at 0:15 am.
Everyone please take a look!
Please give me a money check for the time that has passed.
please
Wow!
Great.
But you can't.
can live with (a person)
gulp
oooh
clean
Not too shiny.
oh no (used as an expression of despair or when giving up)
Yummy!
What's broken?
Too cold.
Wow, that's perfect!
Eat it while it's still warm!
Bon appétit!
Horse!
What could be better?
A body that stings.
delicious
highest
Rice can be this delicious.
It'll warm you up.
It's so cold today.
But I'm already cold enough.
It's already damp.
feel depressed
I thought it was a hot spring when I took my first bite.
What kind of food report strike?
We had dinner.
(not) at all
Shall we go to bed?
Let's have tea and sleep together.
I'm fine.
everyone
I'll take this one then.
I prefer this one.
Then between these two.
Between? cold (e.g. weather)
Don't turn around.
frightening
turn towards us
Good luck turning it off.
I heard there's a button.
Button on top.
I'll go.
gradual
Turn it off. Turn it off faster.
No, it's a step-by-step system.
Yeah, it's fine.
Don't do that.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't do it.
Yeah. Feels good.